Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Young Duke, you really went all out.
أيها الدوق الشاب، لقد بذلت قصارى جهدك حقًا.
This hidden weapon is so powerful.
هذا السلاح المخفي قوي جدًا.
What's its name?
ما اسمه؟
Gatling.
جاتلينج.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
This is the mini Gatling.
هذه هي جاتلينج الصغيرة.
There's an even stronger one.
هناك واحد أقوى.
But Your subject hasn't built it yet.
ولكن موضوعك لم يبنيه بعد
Good.
جيد.
Quick, draw it for us.
سريعًا، ارسمها لنا.
Let us see it.
دعونا نرى ذلك.
Yes.
نعم.
Sir.
سيد.
Did you find out where that kid
هل عرفت أين هذا الطفل؟
got his weapon?
هل حصل على سلاحه؟
I sent people all over the capital.
أرسلت الناس إلى كافة أنحاء العاصمة.
No one knows.
لا أحد يعلم.
Only Shi Feifan has it.
فقط شي فيفان لديه ذلك.
Such a fine weapon.
هذا سلاح جيد.
I must get my hands on it.
يجب أن أضع يدي عليه.
Just... just this little thing?
فقط... فقط هذا الشيء الصغير؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
this is called Gatling Plus.
هذا ما يسمى بـ Gatling Plus.
Within five hundred meters, nothing survives.
في نطاق خمسمائة متر، لا يبقى شيء على قيد الحياة.
What is five hundred meters?
ما هو خمسمائة متر؟
It's a unit of measurement.
إنها وحدة قياس.
It converts to one li.
يتم تحويله إلى لي واحد.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Your subject would never joke.
موضوعك لن يمزح أبدًا.
Your subject has even stronger weapons.
موضوعك لديه أسلحة أقوى.
Like airplanes,
مثل الطائرات،
tanks,
الدبابات،
and aircraft carriers.
وحاملات الطائرات.
Hurry, hurry!
اسرع اسرع!
Draw all of these quickly.
ارسم كل هذا بسرعة.
Let us see.
دعونا نرى.
Yes.
نعم.
Such magical hidden weapons exist?
هل توجد مثل هذه الأسلحة السحرية المخفية؟
Make all of these at once.
اصنع كل هذا مرة واحدة.
Drive the Qiang Country envoys out of our land.
طرد مبعوثي دولة تشيانغ من أرضنا.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
making these weapons will take some time.
إن تصنيع هذه الأسلحة سيستغرق بعض الوقت.
But Your subject has a way
ولكن موضوعك له طريقة
to make them leave
لجعلهم يغادرون
without giving them any excuse.
دون أن نعطيهم أي عذر.
We grant you time.
نحن نمنحك الوقت.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
شكرا لك جلالتك.
If Your subject completes the task,
إذا أكمل موضوعك المهمة،
may Your subject receive a reward?
هل يمكن لموضوعك أن يحصل على مكافأة؟
Granted.
ممنوح.
Wait.
انتظر.
Next time you come,
في المرة القادمة التي تأتي فيها،
can you bring that
هل يمكنك احضار ذلك؟
Gatling Plus
جاتلينج بلس
for us to see?
لكي نرى؟
Your subject will try, will try.
سوف يحاول موضوعك، سوف يحاول.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
The Qiang Country matter is serious.
قضية بلاد تشيانغ خطيرة.
Are you really letting the Young Duke
هل تسمحين للدوق الشاب حقًا؟
"Shi" means mountain.
"شي" تعني الجبل.
His roots are solid as rock.
جذوره صلبة كالصخر.
Maybe he'll become a true gem.
ربما سيصبح جوهرة حقيقية.
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
That Plus,
هذا بالإضافة إلى ذلك،
can you really make it?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك حقا؟
Just talk big for now, worry later.
فقط تحدث بصوت عال الآن، ولا تقلق لاحقًا.
Big talk? Why now of all times?
كلام كبير؟ لماذا الآن تحديدًا؟
Fan'er.
المشجعين.
What punishment did His Majesty give?
ما هو العقاب الذي فرضه جلالته؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Father can handle it.
الأب يستطيع التعامل مع هذا الأمر.
Duke.
دوق.
His Majesty praised the Young Duke.
وأشاد جلالته بالدوق الشاب.
Really?
حقًا؟
Is this really my son?
هل هذا حقا ابني؟
He truly has grown up.
لقد كبر حقا.
Get ready.
استعد.
The show is about to start.
العرض على وشك أن يبدأ.
Cunning Southerners.
الجنوبيون الماكرون.
Spit it out, don't hold back.
ابصقه، لا تتردد.
His Majesty has issued a decree.
أصدر جلالته مرسوما.
Commander Linggou Shi Feifan lacks virtue.
القائد Linggou Shi Feifan يفتقر إلى الفضيلة.
He overstepped his bounds.
لقد تجاوز حدوده.
His pay is docked for half a year.
تم خصم راتبه لمدة نصف عام.
He must apologize to you.
يجب عليه أن يعتذر لك.
Apologize?
يعتذر؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
Right now, Commander Shi
في الوقت الحالي، القائد شي
just got scolded at the palace.
لقد تم توبيخي للتو في القصر.
He's at the best restaurant in the Southern Dynasty
إنه في أفضل مطعم في سلالة الجنوب
setting up an apology banquet for you.
إعداد مأدبة اعتذار لك.
Brother, you honor me by coming today.
أخي، لقد شرفتني بتواجدك اليوم.
It's truly my honor.
إنه شرف لي حقا.
Commander Shi.
القائد شي.
We met through conflict, now we know each other.
التقينا من خلال الصراع، والآن نعرف بعضنا البعض.
A pleasure, a pleasure.
متعة، متعة.
I heard you, Brother, in Qiang Country,
لقد سمعتك يا أخي في بلاد تشيانغ،
fought tigers in the south,
قاتل النمور في الجنوب،
kicked dragons in the north.
ركل التنانين في الشمال.
I admire you.
أنا معجب بك.
You flatter me, Brother Shi.
لقد أطرتني يا أخي شي.
Today, I accept you as my brother.
اليوم أقبلك كأخي.
Come, good brother.
تعال يا أخي الصالح.
Drink!
شرب!
Brother Shi.
الأخ شي.
That powerful weapon last time,
هذا السلاح القوي في المرة الأخيرة،
could you let me see it?
هل يمكن أن تسمح لي برؤيته؟
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
the Emperor took it back.
استعادها الإمبراطور.
He said
قال
he was afraid I'd misfire
كان خائفا من أن أخطئ في إطلاق النار
and hurt you, Brother.
وأؤذيك يا أخي.
That's a shame.
إنه لأمر مؤسف.
Not a shame.
ليس عيبا.
There will be chances later.
ستكون هناك فرص لاحقًا.
Brother.
أخ.
Come.
يأتي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Will this really work?
هل سيعمل هذا حقا؟
You'll see soon.
سوف ترى قريبا.
Princess, please come in.
الأميرة، من فضلك ادخلي.
Princess.
أميرة.
Since our countries are marrying,
وبما أن بلداننا تتزوج،
Brother, don't you want to see the Princess's face?
أخي ألا تريد رؤية وجه الأميرة؟
Please.
لو سمحت.
This is your princess.
هذه أميرتك.
So, Brother, what do you think?
إذن يا أخي، ما رأيك؟
Has the princess's beauty stunned you?
هل أذهلكم جمال الأميرة؟
Look at the princess's eyes.
أنظر إلى عيون الأميرة.
Hold me, I need to rest my feet.
احتضني، فأنا بحاجة إلى راحة قدمي.
They're truly dazzling.
إنهم مبهرون حقا.
One glance and your Khan is bewitched.
نظرة واحدة وسيُسحر خانك.
Now look at the princess's teeth.
الآن أنظر إلى أسنان الأميرة.
They're like stars in the sky.
إنهم مثل النجوم في السماء.
Far apart from each other.
بعيدين عن بعضهم البعض.
Yet they echo one another.
ومع ذلك فإنهم يرددون صدى بعضهم البعض.
Her features each have their own charm.
كل ملامحها لها سحرها الخاص.
It gives her a unique allure.
فهو يعطيها جاذبية فريدة من نوعها.
Our princess is a real treasure.
أميرتنا هي كنز حقيقي.
Amazing! Help me inside, quick.
رائع! ساعدوني للدخول بسرعة.
Brother Shi.
الأخ شي.
Your Southern Dynasty's taste
ذوق سلالتك الجنوبية
is truly one of a kind.
هو حقا فريد من نوعه.
With such beauty,
مع هذا الجمال،
your Khan marrying her
خانك يتزوجها
is a real blessing.
إنها نعمة حقيقية.
Don't worry, Brother.
لا تقلق يا أخي.
I promise to help you with this task.
أعدك بأن أساعدك في هذه المهمة.
Brother, what's wrong?
أخي ما المشكلة؟
Is the food not to your liking?
هل الطعام لا يعجبك؟
Brother.
أخ.
Sir.
سيد.
Brother, what's the matter?
أخي ما الأمر؟
Is it the food that's not good?
هل الطعام ليس جيدا؟
The marriage alliance was just a rash remark.
وكان تحالف الزواج مجرد تعليق متهور.
It doesn't count.
لا يهم.
Where's the wine?
أين النبيذ؟
Bring the wine.
احضر النبيذ.
Brother.
أخ.
Today,
اليوم،
we won't leave until we're drunk.
لن نغادر حتى نكون في حالة سُكر.
How about it, Brother?
ماذا عنك يا أخي؟
Lord Xue.
اللورد شيو.
It's your turn now.
الآن دورك .
At your command.
تحت أمرك.
Shi Feifan, let's see what you'll do next.
شي فيفان، دعنا نرى ما ستفعله بعد ذلك.
We're screwed, got too drunk.
لقد أصبحنا في ورطة كبيرة، لقد أصبحنا في حالة سكر شديد.
Urgent news from the palace.
أخبار عاجلة من القصر.
His Majesty will send troops to Qiang Country.
جلالته سيرسل قوات إلى بلاد تشيانغ.
In just this short time,
في هذا الوقت القصير فقط،
His Majesty is about to attack Qiang Country.
جلالته على وشك مهاجمة بلاد تشيانغ.
His Majesty said,
وقال جلالته:
Qiang Country is troubled inside and out.
بلاد تشيانغ تعاني من مشاكل داخلية وخارجية.
His Majesty has reached an agreement with Qing Country.
لقد توصل جلالته إلى اتفاق مع دولة تشينغ.
A Gatling for an alliance between two nations.
جاتلينج للتحالف بين دولتين.
This is a great opportunity.
هذه فرصة عظيمة.
We must not ally.
لا ينبغي لنا أن نتحالف.
I just became brothers with him.
لقد أصبحنا أخوة معه.
No matter what, I have to help him.
مهما كان الأمر، يجب علي أن أساعده.
Just your word alone—
فقط كلمتك وحدها؟؟؟
How would His Majesty agree?
فكيف سيوافق جلالته؟
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Unless what?
إلا ماذا؟
Qiang Country gives up tribute and marriage alliance.
دولة تشيانغ تتخلى عن الجزية وتحالف الزواج.
Sir, Qing Country's envoy is here too.
سيدي، مبعوث دولة تشينغ موجود هنا أيضًا.
I'm afraid we won't be coming back.
أخشى أننا لن نعود.
Brother Shi, no need for marriage alliance.
أخي شي، ليس هناك حاجة إلى تحالف الزواج.
No need for tribute either.
لا حاجة للجزية أيضًا.
We—we're leaving now.
نحن نغادر الآن.
Brother.
أخ.
If Brother leaves now,
إذا غادر الأخ الآن،
I can't explain to His Majesty.
لا أستطيع أن أشرح لجلالته.
Brother Shi, please accept this.
أخي شي، من فضلك تقبل هذا.
How could I accept this?
كيف يمكنني أن أقبل هذا؟
Brother Shi, it's just a small token.
أخي شي، إنها مجرد رمز صغير.
When I return to Qiang Country,
عندما أعود إلى بلاد تشيانغ،
I'll send ten thousand taels of gold.
سأرسل عشرة آلاف تايل من الذهب.
No one believes you'll return.
لا أحد يصدق أنك ستعود.
That's not necessary.
هذا ليس ضروريا.
Brother.
أخ.
I think Fan Lou
أعتقد أن فان لو
is pretty nice.
إنه لطيف جدًا.
Buy it.
اشتريه.
Brother, you're truly generous.
أخي، أنت كريم حقًا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Take care, Brother.
اعتني بنفسك يا أخي.
Brother Xue.
الأخ شيويه.
You deserve the Oscar Best Actor.
أنت تستحق جائزة الأوسكار لأفضل ممثل.
Osc—Osc—Oscar what?
أوسك؟؟؟أوسك؟؟؟أوسكار ماذا؟
I'm praising your acting.
أنا أشيد بتمثيلك.
It's all thanks to Commander Linggou's direction.
كل هذا بفضل توجيهات القائد لينغو.
By the way, His Majesty is still waiting.
وبالمناسبة جلالته لا زال ينتظر.
No time to waste.
لا يوجد وقت لنضيعه.
Commander Linggou, you should hurry to the palace.
القائد لينغو، يجب عليك أن تسرع إلى القصر.
What's the rush?
ما هو الاندفاع؟
It's getting late.
لقد أصبح الوقت متأخرًا.
I'm heading home to sleep.
أنا متجه إلى المنزل للنوم.
Sleep?
ينام؟
But what if the Qiang envoy
ولكن ماذا لو كان مبعوث تشيانغ
gets suspicious?
يصبح مشبوهًا؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
With his brain capacity,
بفضل قدرته العقلية،
he won't figure it out even back in Qiang Country.
لن يتمكن من فهم الأمر حتى في بلد تشيانغ.
A long, endless night.
ليلة طويلة لا نهاية لها.
It's hard to endure.
من الصعب التحمل.
This city is so empty.
هذه المدينة فارغة جداً.
These memories are so strong.
هذه الذكريات قوية جدًا.
Are you here to kill me?
هل أنت هنا لتقتلني؟